So you've got
your SRT file with your accurate captions.
Awesome.
Now let's get that uploaded to YouTube.
On your YouTube channel, on the left
hand side, click "Content,"
then scroll to the video
you want to upload the captions to
and click "Details."
So this little pencil icon.
On the left hand
side, click "Subtitles." Now
these captions you're seeing are the auto
generated ones that YouTube made.
Those are no good.
"Add language." Choose your language.
I'm a stickler for detail,
so I'll say "English (United States)."
Under subtitles here...
click "Add."
"Upload file."
"With timing" is very important.
So when it asks you to select
subtitle file type,
"With timing." "Continue."
Go to wherever you have the SRT file
and say Open.
And there it is.
It'll give you a preview window
here so you can get a...
Just to
make sure things are looking good here.
So let's hit play.
[Today we're taking a look at the
HPRC 6300 hard case.
I've been meaning to do this for a while.
I haven't gotten to it just yet.
It is like magic because it's
got the SRT file, all the accurate
captions, it's got the timing,
so you don't have to worry about that.
So that's really it.
Now you go up to here, say "Publish."
And you're good to go.
You can go back to the video.
In the lower right
hand corner, the CC icon.
Click that.
There you go.
It is now live for the world
to see with accurate captions.
Hopefully that helped you guys.
Thanks so much for watching.
I'll see you next time.